export const QuestionEnData = [
  {
    question: "I am not a beauty professional and I want to buy the products, how do I do that?",
    answer: 'In the local tab, you may be able to find a salon closer to you, or look for us on our social networks and we will indicate one of our representatives.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Do you deliver to Whole Brazil?',
    answer: "We deliver. Leave your message in the contact bar and we'll get back to you explaining the whole process."
  },
  {
    question: 'Which line is best suited for oily hair?',
    answer: 'We recommend our Home Care Detox Refresh and Mint with Malva.'
  },
  {
    question: "I'm a beauty professional and I want to buy your products, how do I do that?",
    answer: 'Send us your region through the contact tab and we will indicate the representative in your Ã¡rea'
  },
  {
    question: 'Do you have products for hair schedule?',
    answer: 'Yes, Facinnius has a complete line of hair schedule for you including products for nutrition, hydration, reconstruction and scalp treatment.'
  },
  {
    question: "Why can't I find the Facinnius product in perfumery?",
    answer: 'Because Facinnius focuses on serving beauty professionals, with a team of representatives who serve professionals in their establishments. But you can get the products at salons that resell the Facinnius home care line.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What would be Home Care line products?',
    answer: 'It is a line of products that you can use at home with the same quality and efficiency as in the salon, but in smaller packages to continue the hair treatment.'
  },
  {
    question: "I'm black, I have highlights, can I use the Violeta Seda Protein Facinnius line?",
    answer: 'Yes, because the Kit Violeta Seda Protein Facinnius is indicated for all types of locks.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can Facinnius shampoos be used on children?',
    answer: 'Yes, but we recommend that you read our precautions for use on the back of the package.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Does the use of combing cream rule out the use of conditioner?',
    answer: 'Generally, combing creams have different characteristics from conditioners and are products that do not need rinsing, such as leave-in, with softening and treatment properties. Conditioners should never be replaced, as they have a specific action of electrically rebalancing recently washed strands.'
  },
  {
    question: 'How to apply the Facinnius Sea and Pool Silicone Milk leave-in correctly?',
    answer: 'Silicone milk is a Leave-in Finisher with high UVA/UVB protection power, leaving your hair protected and hydrated. It is recommended to apply it over the entire length of the strands thirty minutes before exposure to the sun.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are Facinnius treatment masks for?',
    answer: 'Masks are products aimed at replacing substances that the hair lost or due to climatic factors, incorrect use of chemical products, excess heat from flat irons and dryers, in addition to other mechanical actions (brushing, tying). Conditioners, on the other hand, are cosmetics that serve to rebalance the hair strands that, in the process of washing with shampoo, become impregnated with negative charges. The use of masks does not rule out the use of conditioners.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I apply Infinity One Facinnius Biphasic on wet hair?',
    answer: 'Yes, dry or wet hair must be clean. Apply a sufficient amount to all strands and finish as usual. No need to rinse and shake before use.'
  },{
    question: 'What is the difference between Acezzo aerosol and Acezzo liquid?',
    answer: 'None, the formulation of both products are the same. What differentiates the two products is applicability. With liquid Acezzo, you spray a small amount on your hands and spread it along the length of the hair. For Acezzo aerosol, we apply the jet at a distance directly to the hair.'
  },
  {
    question: 'I have progressive, does Facinnius have a specific line?',
    answer: 'Yes, we have the effect liss line that includes shampoo, conditioner and leave-in that was developed for chemically treated hair, that is a post-progressive product.'
  },
  {
    question: "What is Kolore's whitening background color?",
    answer: 'Our Kolore Facinnius professional coloring has a cold violet lightening background. For information on the subject you will find on our social networks.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Does Facinnius products nano technology?',
    answer: 'We have some lines with nano technology, this is the case of the Effect liss line, Infinity One Line, Infinity One Gold Line, Infinity Repair Protein Line and all our leave-in are some examples.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Does Facinnius have organic progressive?',
    answer: 'We have our Ilummini Volume Reducer which is indicated for the creation of organic progressives, a formaldehyde-free product.'
  },
];